freevector.com 2011-06-23

# FREE VECTOR PRIVACY

Welcome to Free Vector!

 **PRIVACY POLICY**

Free Vector's Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by Free Vector, located at www.freevector.com.

Free Vector has implemented all reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of personal information that we control. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Free Vector and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its third parties.

We collect personal information when you provide it to us by becoming a Free Vector member, when you sign up to receive our newsletters, participate in forum discussions, send us messages or emails or when you download or buy one of our products. By using or accessing Free Vector, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

When you become a Free Vector member, you create your own profile, which contains certain personal information, such as your name, nickname, your gender, your address, your email address and any other information that you provide to us. Your member information, as well as your (nick)name, email and avatar, are displayed to other people visiting the Free Vector website.

Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, marketplace listings or other items, this information may become publicly available.

Free Vector site usage information is occasionally collected automatically about your activities while visiting the Free Vector site, including what pages you view and when you view them and information about the browser you are using.

You agree and understand that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with any account you use to access the Free Vector website and services. Accordingly, you agree that you will be solely responsible for all activities that occur under your Free Vector account. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password or of your account, you agree to notify Free Vector immediately at “info at freevector dot com”.

 **USE OF INFORMATION**

Profile information you submit to Free Vector will be available to visitors of the website and limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. Free Vector may send you website-related announcements from time to time. Generally, you may opt out of such emails by unsubscribing to our email updates.

Free Vector may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) permitted by you 2) reasonably necessary to offer the service or 3) legally requested as we might be required to disclose user information in compliance with applicable laws.

We may use third parties to facilitate our operations, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these activities.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Free Vector-specified purposes.

We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through on-site offers. We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other websites, brands or companies.

 **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

Advertisements that appear on Free Vector are sometimes served directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked.

Free Vector does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Free Vector unless you choose to share it with them.

 **SECURITY**

Free Vector takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as Paypal password or credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

 **CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION**

Access and control over most personal information on Free Vector is readily available through the profile editing tools. Free Vector users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Free Vector account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available.

 **UNDER AGE 13 POLICY**

Free Vector does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to become a member. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Free Vector. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Free Vector or send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

 **BETWEEN AGES 13-18 POLICY**

Free Vector recommends that minors 13-18 years old ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet

 **LINKS**

Free Vector may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 15, 2010. We may revise these policies at any time. Questions? Please direct questions regarding this Privacy Policy to “info at freevector dot com”.
